{
    "id": "65e3049e0e144254bc437905cc93ca86",
    "title": "Time Expressions | Already, Yet, Still",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The servant has …………… left the house.",
            "description": "Already means sooner than expected. ",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet",
                "still"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0c9752f5cf4d4417a95bbda079dfc72c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of lives have ……………………. been lost.",
            "description": "Already means sooner than expected. Already refers to past or present.",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ba7cb60f90f446dfb93ee0be41e1aed1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ………………….. visited Australia?",
            "description": "Ever means at any point of time.",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "still",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08775d2fb96d476d853c49774e760694"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don’t you wear a coat ………………….. in winter?",
            "description": "Even is used to emphasize extremes.",
            "answers": [
                "still",
                "even",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "687f64ffa6b04b61a45329aef00ecb7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………. late for work.",
            "description": "Never means at no point of time.",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c864dbd8135f45198a12df50e21dccca"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have not ……………………. heard from them.",
            "description": "Not yet is used to say that an expected thing is in the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "still",
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "616596701ee140d39480e844d4bb38de"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………. asleep.",
            "description": "Still is used to talk about something that is not finished. ",
            "answers": [
                "still",
                "yet",
                "even"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "276c0cc445ce46998bb36c83d66f0c27"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been thinking for hours, but I …………………….. can’t decide.",
            "description": "Still means something is not finished.",
            "answers": [
                "still",
                "yet",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "122ed7dadc714be48684e13fb36a9ffc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ………………….. finished?",
            "description": "Already means sooner than expected. ",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet",
                "still"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d047b6e5fc24ce1a3e1751c1867ba03"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you called the supervisor, ……………………?",
            "description": "In questions yet is used to ask whether something expected has happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already",
                "still"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b3add30b3f5425a9e5debdedb781f12"
        },
        {
            "question": "The oranges aren’t ripe …………………..",
            "description": "Not yet is used to say that an expected thing is in the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet",
                "still"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d31957059224937a308fb29e84966c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The guests have ………………….. arrived.",
            "description": "Already means sooner than expected. ",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "still",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e7b57c202d24e598244efd3c5278695"
        }
    ]
}